<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">TipsAndTricks</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    <string name="multiplication">
<![CDATA[
<p> <b>Multiplication</b> </p>
<p> <b>Example : 43 x 78</b> </p>
<p><b> Step 1 : Finding the Units digit</b></p>
<p> The first objective would be to get the units digit. 
In order to do this we just need to multiply the units digit of both the numbers. thus, 3 x 8 would give us 24. 
Hence, we would write 4 in the units digit of the answer and carry over the digit 2 to the tens place as follows </p>
<p>&nbsp&nbsp  43<br />x  78<br />______<br />&nbsp&nbsp&nbsp&nbsp   4 <br/> 2 carry over to the tens place.</p>  
<p>   At this point we know that the units digit is 4 and also that there is a carry over of 2 to the 
tens place of the answer.</p>
<p><b> Step 2 : Finding the tens place digit</b></p>
<p>&nbsp&nbsp  43<br />x  78<br />______<br />&nbsp&nbsp&nbsp 5 4 <br/>5 carry over to hundereds place.<br /><br />
<b> Thought process :</b><br />
 4 x 8 + 3 x 7 = 32 + 21 = 53<br /> 53 + 2 ( from carry over ) = 55<br /> Thus we write 5 in the tens place and carry over 5 to hundereds place</p>
<p> In the above case, we have multiplied the units digit of the second number with the tens digit of the first number and added the multiplication of the units digit
of the first number with the tens digit of the second number. Thus we would get : <br /><br /> 8 ( units of digit of the second number ) x 4 ( tens digit of the first number ) + 7
( tens digit of the second number ) x 3 ( Units digit of the first number ) + 2 ( caryy over over from the units digit calculation ).<br />
    = 32 + 21 + 2 = 55.<br />
 &nbsp&nbsp We write down 5 in the tens digit of th answer and carry over 5 to the hundereds digit of the answer.</p>
 <p><b> Step 3 : Finding hundereds place digit</b></p>
 <p>&nbsp&nbsp  43<br />x  78<br />______<br />3 3 5 4 <br/>
 <b> Thought Process :</b><br /><br />            4 x 7 = 28<br />            28 + 5 = 33<br />   Since, 4 & 7 are the last digits on the left in both the numbers
 this is the last calculation in this problem and hence we can write 33 for the remaining 2 digits in the answer.<br />Thus, the answer to the question is 3 3 5 4.</p>
 

]]>
    </string>

</resources>